



Mamadnazarov Iskandar

Male, 33 years old, born on 24 April 1987

+7 (915) 2199914 — preferred means of communication iskandarko@gmail.com

Reside in: Moscow, metro station Voykovskaya Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia Ready to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

Web developer

IT, Internet, Telecom

- Software Development
- Web Engineer
- · Web master

Employment: project work, part time, full time

Work schedule: remote working, flexible schedule, full day, shift schedule

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 11 years 9 months

August 2019 — till now 1 year 3 months

Kaspersky

Moscow, www.kaspersky.ru

Technical Writer

Job duties

- working texts for B2B products of Kaspersky (KSC, KSWS, KICS, KESS, KEA, MDR, KATA, KEDR Optimum and others);
- developing guides and other documentation on English and Russian languaes;
- developing texts and layouts for applications' GUI;
- fixing bugs;
- communicating with the development team.

September 2012 till now 8 years 2 months

SIBUR

www.sibur.ru

Lead Engineering Coordinator

Job duties:

- coordination of activities related to engineering, procurement, project implementation;
- review of internal and external correspondence;
- development of procedures and technical specifications;
- conducting contract negotiations, development of contract technical exhibits;
- development of reference and analytical materials for the management of the company;
- development of presentations;
- communication with a group of engineers, tracking of tasks deadlines, conducting clarification meetings;
- negotiation with contractors and vendors;

Completed projects:

- ZapSib-2 (petrochemical plant in Tobolsk)
- Amur GCC (gas chemical plant in Svobodny)

September 2009 — June 2012 Keldysh Center, FSUE

www.kerc.msk.ru/

Intern

Job duties:

- development of design documentation for the experimental unit for growing of carbon nanotubes;
- performing required calculations;
- conducting experiments on the unit;

Results:

- based on the results, a graduation work was written;
- an article on the topic of carbon nanotubes was published with my co-authorship.

June 2007 — February 2008 9 months

Asteros

www.asteros.ru

Chief Consultant of the Service and Outsourcing Department

Job duties

- support users on IBM, Hewlet Packard, and other products;
- development of manuals and educational documentation for new employees;
- compiling of reports on the work done.

Results:

- helped the company with development of the new technical support department;

Education

Master

2012

Bauman Moscow State Technical University, Moscow

Mechanical Engineering technologies, electronic technologies in mechanical engineering, Engineer

Key skills

Languages

Russian — Native

English — C1 — Advanced

Skills

Business English Software Development C++ HTML HTML5 CSS

JavaScript Python Time management Business communication

Business Correspondence Contracts Negotiation Negotiation skills

Project management Communication skills CSS3 Node.js React.js

Further information

About me

Having a masters degree in Electronics Engineering I worked for an engineering company for 7 years. I've started learning web development in 2018, though programming has been my passion since high school.

At the moment I have experience in building modern websites and web applications, using public APIs, configuring databases, working with React framework and other JS and CSS libraries.

Fluent in English, communicative, team worker, attentive to details, easily master new knowledge and skills, like to solve problems.

I'm eager to apply my skills on a new project.

In my free time I travel, shoot and edit video. Married, raising two children.